mobile57.com 2017-07-08

# Privacy Policy - Mobile57

Privacy policy deal with the manner with which Mobile57 would collect, store, use or disclose personal information of our user / users from the website (site) www.mobile57.com. The privacy policy mentioned below is applicable to complete website and all the products and services offered by Mobile57.

**Personal identification information**

Mobile57.com may collect some personal information of the users using the site in a variety of way. The information collected may include but are not limited to, information entered by user / users during their navigation on the site, entering information to fill any forms etc. User / users might need to provide their true name, email address and other relevant information for some services, which otherwise they might not be able to use.

Personal identification information from users are only collected voluntarily (if they submit these information). Mobile57 offer its users to refrain submitting any personal information which they seem intimidating, except that not submitting these information might refrain them from specific site services / activities.

**Non-Personal identification information**

Apart from personal information that need to be submitted voluntarily, we may collect some non-personal identification information at our dispense, whenever you visit our website (www.mobile57.com). These information might include but not limited to, name of computer, browser information, technical information, IP address, operating system and other relevant information.

**Cookies**

Mobile57 uses cookies to provide enhanced user experience to our visitors / users. These cookies are stored on your storage device for record-keeping. These cookies might also be used for tracking purpose. You can stop receiving cookies through your browser function. However, if your browser refuse to accept cookies, you might not be able to use specific parts of the website with full functionalities.

**Use of information**

Information collected by Mobile57 might be used for following purposes:  Enhance the user experience of our website – we always appreciate your feedback and constantly improve our site’s navigation and user experience as per your feedback  Marketing / communication – We often use your email address to update you with latest news and happenings on our site. We further use your email to contact you for any query, question or respond to your requests

**Privacy Protection**

Mobile57 adapts the highest measures to ensure protection of your personal and other data at all times. We comply with highest safety measures to negate any unauthorized access, distortion, alteration or destruction of collected data including user name, password etc.

**Use of Personal Information**

Mobile57 never trade, rent or sell your personal data to any other third party. However, any generic statistical or aggregated data that in no way represent any personal identification of our users or partners or visitors might be shared with our trustworthy associates and advertisers. The reason for sharing statistical and aggregated data with our associates are advertisers are mentioned above.

**Advertising**

You might receive certain advertisements from our partners. These advertisements might contain cookies that will be saved to your storage device, for the purpose of recognizing and enhancing the user experience. These cookies will be used to recognize you every time you visit our website and also to compile a non-personal generic and statistical advertising targeted data. These information will primarily be used by relevant and trusted advertisement agencies to send you targeted updates and advertisements that they believe you will most likely be interested in. The privacy policy of Mobile57 isn’t in anyway responsible to represent the cookie policy of any advertiser.

**Google AdSense**

You might be receiving certain advertisements served by Google. Google advertisements are based on their DART cookies which collect non-personal data and don’t track any of your personal information including name, email address, phone number, home address etc. You can stop accepting these cookies by visiting privacy policy of Google ad at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

Mobile57 has its sole discretion to modify, alter, update or change complete privacy policy at its own consent. However, whenever we will be modifying, altering, updating or changing our privacy policy we will inform you by adding the date at the bootom of our Privacy Policy page. It is therefore advised to you to regularly visit our privacy policy to better comply with our standards and regulations on your personal and non-personal data collection and use. By visiting the website, you are admitting it as your responsibility to regularly visit privacy policy terms and adhere to our policy at all times.

**User Consent**

By visiting www.mobile57.com, you are accepting our privacy policy wholly and giving your consent to adhere to this. If in any case you do not accept or are not agree with our policy, you are requested to stop using our website immediately. Your use of site is taken as consent of agreement to our policies.

**Contact Us**

You can always contact us for any updates or queries regarding privacy policy or any other dealing on www.mobile57.com. We will be pleased to answer all your queries and questions.
